http://www.milpower.com/privacy-policy

HomeProductsDC/DC Power SuppliesDC/DC Holdup UnitsAC/DC Power SuppliesAC+DC/DC Power SuppliesDC/AC InvertersVPX VITA 62 SolutionsUninterruptible Power SuppliesPower Distribution UnitsAccessoriesCustom DesignsApplicationsAirborneGroundNavalContact UsGet a quoteRMA RequestCompanyAbout usNewsQuality AssuranceCareers
HomeProductsDC/DC Power SuppliesDC/DC Holdup UnitsAC/DC Power SuppliesAC+DC/DC Power SuppliesDC/AC InvertersVPX VITA 62 SolutionsUninterruptible Power SuppliesPower Distribution UnitsAccessoriesCustom DesignsApplicationsAirborneGroundNavalContact UsGet a quoteRMA RequestCompanyAbout usNewsQuality AssuranceCareers
Privacy Policy
Notice / Scope
This Privacy Policy describes the ways in which Milpower Source collect, store and use information about individual persons who visit this website or submit information to us by other means.
BY SUBMITTING INFORMATION TO US OR BY USING OUR WEBSITE, INCLUDING ANY TOOLS, YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION AS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. YOU ALSO ACKNOWLEDGE THAT Milpower Source MAY PERIODICALLY CHANGE, MODIFY, ADD OR REMOVE OR OTHERWISE UPDATE THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ITS DISCRETION, WITHOUT PRIOR NOTIFICATION.
We may decide to change this privacy policy from time to time. We therefore invite you to consult this policy from time to time to familiarize yourself with any changes.
What Data/Information collected
The data we collect online when using our website depends on how you decide to use our website or services. If you simply browse our website, you do not need to enter any personal information.
If you want product-specific information, such as white papers, reports, detailed datasheets, offers, etc., then we will need your personal information. These can be name, company address, phone, email address, etc.
How we handle your Data
We take the protection of your personal data very seriously. We treat your personal data as confidential and in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations and this privacy policy. If you use this website, various pieces of personal data will be collected. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. Please note that data transmitted via the internet (e.g. via email communication) may be subject to security breaches.
Complete protection of your data from third-party access is not possible. We will not sell, share, or otherwise distribute your Personal Data to third parties except as provided in this Privacy Policy.
Protecting your Data (processing, storing)
In order to maintain the integrity and security of your personal information, we have implemented appropriate administrative and technical security procedures to help up protect the personal information in which you supply us and we store this information on non-public computer systems with redundant firewall and password protection to prevent access by anyone other than authorized Milpower Source employees.
In all of our efforts to ensure your confidentiality regarding the use of our website and personal information, as it relates to the GDPR standards, no website can guarantee total security.
Cookies and Analytics
We may collect and process information about your visit our website, such as the pages you visit, the website you came from and some of the searches you perform. Such information is used by us to help improve the contents of the site, to map usage patterns and to compile aggregate statistics about individuals using our site for internal, market research purposes. In doing this, we may install cookies that collect the domain name of the user, your internet service provider, your operating system, and the date and time of access. Most Web browsers are set up to accept cookies, although you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.
We may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We store log files of these IP addresses for administrative, security and statistical purposes.
External Links to other sites
Our websites contains links to a number of websites which we believe may be of interest to our visitors. We aim to ensure that such websites are of the highest standard. However, this Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites and we cannot guarantee the privacy standards of websites to which we link or be responsible for the contents of non-Milpower Source sites. We strongly encourage you to review the privacy policies of any website that you may be directed to.
Milpower Source Inc.
P.O. Box 8107 Field LaneBelmont, NH 03220United States
P: (603) 267-8865
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Categories
DC/DC Power SuppliesDC/DC Holdup UnitsAC/DC Power SuppliesAC+DC/DC Power SuppliesDC/AC InvertersVPX VITA 62 SolutionsUninterruptible Power SuppliesPower Distribution UnitsAccessoriesCustom Designs
About Us Contact SupportMarketing
Conflict Mineral Policy
© 2020 Milpower Source, Inc. | Military Power Supplies
Legal NoticePrivacy PolicyTerms and Conditions
Created by Mark Media Group
